<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wikipedia article interlinkage on The structure of the Cold War on Wikipedia</title><link>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/</link><description>Recent content in Wikipedia article interlinkage on The structure of the Cold War on Wikipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conclusion</title><link>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/conclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/conclusion/</guid><description>In this work we successfully found structure in a vaguely labelled giant of knowledge known as wikipedia. Most of Wikipedia knowledge is connected through references and not tags or labels, a problem which makes text analysis non-trivial.
We have successfully used networks as the glue needed for a meaningful analysis of scattered wikipedia pages. The TF-IDF analysis and wordcloud representations of communities meets or even exceeds our expectations of how much meaning can be extracted with what is comparatively simple and quick methods.</description></item><item><title>Network Description and Analysis</title><link>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/network-analysis/</guid><description>For the research questions of this project, a graph is a suitable representation of the data. It allows us to describe each wikipedia page as a node, and a reference as a link to another node.
Attributes The data we have collected for each page is added as attributes to the nodes in the graph, so we can easily analyse data on the graph after applying methods that filter and group nodes.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dribo.github.io/DTU-02467_ProjectB/text-analysis/</guid><description>Text Analysis The text we have analysed is from the introductory paragraphs of each of the articles. We picked this text because we wanted to capture the essence of the article without having to analyse all the available text. Some of these texts are longer than others, but in general they all capture the essence of the article.
Below is an excerpt of the introductory paragraphs from the article about US president Richard Nixon.</description></item></channel></rss>